{
	"items": [
		{
			"name": "Trump",
			"scenarios": [
				{
					"question": "Choose the best subject",
					"background": "You are writing an email to your teacher about the exam.",
					"options": ["Help Please", "Question Re Exam", "Exam Help"],
					"correct": "Question Re Exam"
				},
				{
					"question": "Choose the best subject",
					"background": "You recently studied abroad in New Zealand and stayed with a host family. The host family were very kind to you. You are writing an email to thank you.",
					"options": ["Back in Japan", "Hello", "Thank you so much!"],
					"correct": "Thank you so much!"
				},
				{
					"question": "Choose the best subject",
					"background": "You are sending an email to a university friend in Japan. Your friend does not speak Japanese. You want to invite your friend out to a party on Saturday.",
					"options": ["Saturday Night", "Yeah!!!", "Oi"],
					"correct": "Saturday Night"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "Certificate",
			"scenarios": [
				{
					"question": "Choose the best greeting",
					"background": "You are writing an email to your teacher to ask for more time to complete an assignment. Your teacher’s name is John Blake (Blake is his surname)",
					"options": ["Dear A/Prof Blake,", "Dear Professor John,", "Dear A/Prof Blake John,"],
					"correct": "Dear A/Prof Blake,"
				},
				{
					"question": "Choose the best greeting",
					"background": "You are sending an email to your English-speaking friend from UoA. Her name is Carol Swain.",
					"options": ["Dear Ms. Swain,", "Hi Carol,", "Hello Swain san,"],
					"correct": "Hi Carol,"
				},
				{
					"question": "Choose the best greeting",
					"background": "You are sending an email to an English-speaking student from UoA. You have not met this student. This student is an expert in machine learning. You want to ask the student for help on some machine learning homework. The student’s name is Steve Smith. (Smith is his family name)",
					"options": ["Dear Mr. Smith,", "Hey Steve,", "Dear Steve,"],
					"correct": "Dear Steve,"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "NewZealand",
			"scenarios": [
				{
					"question": "Choose the best self-introduction",
					"background": "You are writing an email to your teacher to ask for more time to complete an assignment. Your teacher’s name is John Blake (Blake is his surname)",
					"options": ["Dear Prof. Wilson, My name is Cameron Green, student number 123123123. I am in your Bridge to Intermediate English class.", "Dear Prof. Wilson, I’m your student.", "Dear Prof. Wilson, I’m in your Bridge to Intermediate class. Your class is excellent."],
					"correct": "Dear Prof. Wilson, My name is Cameron Green, student number 123123123. I am in your Bridge to Intermediate English class."
				},
				{
					"question": "Choose the best self-introduction",
					"background": "You are writing an email to a friend you met at a Computer Science conference in Koriyama.",
					"options": ["Hello Mitchell, This is Shohei. I was wondering if … … …", "Hello Mitchell, We met at a conference last week. I was wondering if … … …", "Hello Mitchell, This is Shohei from the conference in Koriyama. I was wondering if … … …"],
					"correct": "Hello Mitchell, This is Shohei from the conference in Koriyama. I was wondering if … … …"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "Pronounciation",
			"scenarios": [
				{
					"question": "Choose the best way to ask for more time to complete the homework",
					"background": "You are writing an email to your teacher to request more time to complete an assignment. ",
					"options": ["Can you give me more time to submit the homework?", "Please give me more time to submit the homework. I really appreciate your kindness.", "Could you possibly give me more time to submit the homework?"],
					"correct": "Could you possibly give me more time to submit the homework?"
				},
				{
					"question": "Choose the best way to ask them",
					"background": "You are writing an email to your teacher to ask them to borrow a book.",
					"options": ["Would I be able to borrow the book you spoke about during class?", "Please lend me the book you spoke about during class. It sounds very interesting.", "Give me the book please. It sounds very interesting. Thank you."],
					"correct": "Would I be able to borrow the book you spoke about during class?"
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "Toeic",
			"scenarios": [
				{
					"question": "Choose the best way to finish the email",
					"background": "You are finishing an email you wrote to a professor. You asked the professor for more information about an exam.",
					"options": ["Thanks, Shohei Otani", "Kind regards, Shohei Otani", "Goodbye, Shohei Otani"],
					"correct": "Kind regards, Shohei Otani"
				},
				{
					"question": "Choose the best way to finish the email",
					"background": "You are finishing an email you wrote to your friend. You are saying thank you for the help they gave you recently.",
					"options": ["Thanks so much! Shohei", "Your assistance was greatly appreciated. Shoehei Otani", "Sincerely, Shohei"],
					"correct": "Thanks so much! Shohei"
				}
			]
		}
	]
}